天哪
Oh, man.
谁啊  崔格在通洗澡间的下水道
What is that? Treeger's snaking the shower drain.
这是什么鬼东西
What in the name of hell?
可能他找到了你的夹脚拖鞋
Maybe he found your flip-flop.
嘿  哇
Hey. Whoa.
这是成人A片吗
Is this porn?
我怎么弄的  我一定是按了哪个键了
What did I do? I must have hit something on the remote.
我们有付钱吗
Do we pay for this?
没有  我们连第四台有线的都没付
No, we didn't even pay our cable bill.
也许这是他们的处罚方式
Maybe this is how they punish us.
也许我们应该欠电话费  免费色情电话
Maybe we shouldn't pay our phone bill. Free phone sex.
也许我们还应该欠煤气费
Maybe we shouldn't pay our gas bill.
哇  那女的真是一丝不挂
Whoa, hey, that lady's all kinds of naked.
乔伊不知道按了什么键  它就冒出来了
Yeah, Joey just pressed something on the remote and it just came on.
我有一次也按到过  就是在搜索频道  然后啪出来了
It happened to me once. I was flipping through the channels and, bam.
就像捡到钱一样爽   印有裸体人的钱
It was like finding money. Finding money with naked people on it.
后来我错误地关掉了电视
Then I made the mistake of turning off the TV.
就再也找不回来了
I never got it back again.
我好伤心
And I'm sad.
他干嘛关电视啊
Why would he turn off the TV?
老友记  第四季  第17集  免费成人电影
Friends S04E17  The One With The Free Porn
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
拜托  吃饭一定要看这个吗
All right, you know what? Do we really have to watch this while we eat?
不要  不要
No, no, no.
我们不知道怎么让它消失
We don't know what could make this go away.
对  所以谁也不许碰遥控器  还有电视
Yeah, so no one touches the remote, and no one touches the TV.
也不许碰电视周围的空气
And no one touches the air around the TV.
就像有一个A片保护罩
Imagine a protective porn bubble, if you will.
起码我也要静音  不要  不要
I'm at least going to mute it. No, no, no.
A片还在  还好
We still have porn. Yeah.
嗨  嘿
Hi. Hey.
亲爱的  你干什么
Honey, what are you doing?
这太重了  给我
That's too heavy. Give it here.Yeah.
天哪
Oh, God.
好了
Okay.
我快不行了  实在不能再拖着按摩桌到处跑了
I'm getting too pregnant for this... Lugging around a stupid massage table.
我得找个桌子小点的工作
I have to find a job where I carry a smaller table.
或是不需要桌子的工作
Or a job where you don't have to carry a table.
你是说像医生吗
You mean, like a doctor?
菲比  你挡到A片了啦  让开啊
Pheebs, you're blocking the porn. Look out.
天啊
Oh, my.
这倒提醒我了  我今天要做产检
Oh, that reminds me. I have to see my ob-gyn today.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
艾蜜莉去机场了
So, uh, Emily just went to the airport.
你怎么不送她去
Aw. Why didn't you take her?
她舅舅本来就打算送她
Ehh, her uncle had planned on doing it.
所以  我们说好今天早上道别
And you know, we said our goodbyes this morning, so...
你一定很难受  不过  隔壁有免费的A片看
You must feel horrible. Hey, the guys have free porn.
不了
No.
高兴点  你们会再见面的  对吗
Hey, cheer up. You're gonna see her again, right?
是这样的  我就是不知道
Well, that's the thing. I don't know.
每次我提起她就说
I mean, whenever I brought it up with her, she said:
"这样就很棒啊  何必谈到未来
"This is so fantastic. Why do we have to talk about the future?
就享受现在多好"   别学英国腔
Let's enjoy..." Don't do the accent.
你得再见她一次
You've got to see her again.
干嘛这么在意
Why do you care?
因为
Because.
你可以实现我的幻想
You could get to live out my fantasy.
你对艾蜜莉有幻想
You've had fantasies about Emily?
不是  就是  那个幻想嘛
No. You know, the fantasy.
认识异国他乡的人
Meet someone from a strange land...
疯狂坠入爱河  然后共度余生
...fall madly in love and spend the rest of your lives together.
所以  你国中时
Is that why, in junior high...
老是跟那个乌克兰的男生混
...you were the only one who hung out with that Ukrainian kid?
对  还有他妈妈总是把酸奶油抹在所有吃的上
Yeah, that, but plus his mom used to put sour cream on everything.
你爱她吗
Do you love her?
我们说好只在一起两星期
We said it was only gonna be two weeks, you know?
你爱她
You love her.
什么才是爱
What is love, really?
我就知道你爱她
I knew you loved her.
你得去机场告诉她
You need to go to the airport and tell her.
你会在她登机前追上她
You're probably gonna catch her just as she's about to go to the gate.
你会叫她的名字  大声喊 "我爱你"
You're gonna call out her name and yell, "I love you."
她会说  "我也爱你"
She's gonna say, "I love you too."
然后你们会有最深情的一吻
Then you guys are gonna have the most amazing kiss.
登机门前掌声如雷
Everyone at the gate will applaud.
我是很会接吻的
I am a good kisser.
然后你们钻进驾驶舱
Then you two can sneak into the cockpit.
热血澎湃
Things will start to heat up.
再后来一个空姐进来
And then a stewardess comes in...
我看成人A片太多了
I've been watching too much porn.
那是心跳吗  没错
Is that the heartbeat? That's it.
天哪
Oh, my God.
太酷了
Oh, wow. This is so cool.
我们谈过多胞胎的可能吗
Have we talked about the possibility of multiple births?
先搞定这一胎
Why don't we just take care of this one?
我要是想再怀孕   我会留住你的名片
And should I get pregnant again, I'll hold onto your card, okay?
不是  我听到了三个不同的心跳音
No, I'm getting three separate heartbeats.
三个  你们还担心我一个都怀不上呢
Three? You guys were worried I wouldn't even have one.
医生经常犯错
Doctors are wrong all the time. Well...
你确定有三个
Well, so are you sure that there are three?
绝对的  天哪
Definitely. Oh, my God.
天哪  天哪
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Ha, ha.
再过几个月
So in a few months...
就会有三个孩子在我肚子里转悠
...I'm gonna have three full-grown babies just walking around inside me?
然后他们就像
Oh, oh. And it's gonna be like one of those log rides...
连发炮一样冲出来
...when they just come shooting out.
其实  生三个跟生一个一样
Giving birth to three babies is not that different than giving birth to one.
你懂什么啊
What do you know?
菲比  嗨
Phoebe. Oh! Hi.
产检结果怎样
So how'd it go at the doctor's?
是这样的
Oh, well, okay. Hey.
你知道  你走在街上看见
You know how, when you're, um, walking down the street...
看见三个人并排走
...and you see three people in a row.
你会说  "真好"
And you say "Oh, that's nice."
没错
Yes. Okay.
那么好消息是  你们会有三个孩子
Yeah, well, good news. You're gonna have three babies. Aah!
三个孩子
Three babies? Uh-huh.
啊  哦
Oh, oh!
总算可以组团了
I've finally got my band.
我们会是个大家庭   我一直想要大家庭
We're gonna have a big family! I always wanted a big family!
你们高兴就好  我还怕你们会吓坏了
Oh, God. I'm so glad you guys are happy. I was so afraid you we're gonna be freaked.
为什么要吓坏呢
Oh. Why would we be freaked?
可能因为三个养起来更累也更花钱
No, because maybe it's harder to raise them and the added expense. Ugh!
也对
Oh. Right.
别停   继续高兴  继续高兴
No, back to happy. Back to happy!
不  没问题的
No, no, no. It's gonna be fine...
因为
...because, um...
我教家庭经济学
Because I teach Home Ec.
可以叫三十个学生   一年到头做小孩的衣服
And I can have 30 kids making baby clothes all year long.
就像我专属的廉价童工厂
You know, it'll be like my very own little sweatshop.
你一说我们
You know, I've been thinking
有三个孩子我就在想
ever since you said that we're gonna have triplets.
我最好离开大学去找个工作
The best thing for me to do is drop out of college and get a job.
不  法兰克  你不能放弃学业  不能
Frank. No, you can't quit college. No.
你在念书  真的
You're in college? Really?
冷冻库专校  是的
Yeah, refrigerator college. Yeah.
当我们知道要有孩子了
Yeah, you know, when we found out we were gonna have a baby...
我觉得  我该有个职业  你知道
...I figured, you know, I should have, like, a career, you know?
而且我很喜欢冷冻库
And I love refrigerators. Yeah.
你不能放弃梦想
You can't give up on your dream. Ugh.
不  没关系  我们将有三个孩子
No, it's okay. We're gonna have three kids.
这是另一种梦想
And that's a different kind of dream.
三个孩子   一贫如洗
Three kids and no money.
搭乘009班机的旅客请登机
This is the boarding call for Flight 009.
艾蜜莉
Emily.
天哪  你来干什么
Oh, my God. What are you doing here?
我就是  我得在你走之前再见你一面
I just... I had to see you one more time before you took off.
你真好
You are so sweet.
好大的三角巧克力
That's a big candy bar.
和你一起我度过了最美妙的时光
I had the most amazing time with you.
我也是
Me too.
009班机起飞前最后广播
This is the final boarding call for Flight 009.
那是我的班机
Well, that's me.
给你  拿着这个
Here, have this.
只能有一件登机行李
I'm only allowed one piece of carry-on anyway.
等一下
Wait, uh...
我有事要告诉你
Listen, I have to tell you something.
我一直在想
I've been thinking.
我就直说了  好吧
I'm just going to come out and say it, okay? Uh...
我觉得
I think
我爱你
I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
It's no problem.
这是什么歌  在我脑袋里转悠一天了
What is that song that has been in my head all day?
"蜜桃捕手" 的主题曲
It's the theme from Good Will Humping.
你们知道有谁不喜欢成人A片
You know who doesn't even like dirty movies?
我的新男友约书亚  可不是嘛
My new boyfriend Joshua. Yeah, right.
不  他说了  他喜欢保留一点想像空间
No, he told me he prefers to leave certain things to the imagination.
他有没有说  那些很低俗的对话
Oh, oh, yeah. Did he also say that he thought some of the dialogue was corny?
他会觉得好笑而不是性感
And that he actually found it funny, not sexy?
没错
Yes.
对  他喜欢成人A片
Yeah, he likes porn.
去哪
Where you going?
去看看他是不是真的觉得  超级名模都要太瘦
I'm gonna find out if he really thinks supermodels are too skinny.
嗨  菲比
Hey, Pheebs. Hi.
他们反应如何
Hi. Hey. How'd it go with Frank and Alice?
法兰克得休学
Frank has to quit college...
因为他超级多产的姐姐一次怀上了三胞胎
...because his super-fertile sister is having three babies. Ugh.
我得马上赚一大笔钱
I need to make a lot of money really fast.
而且我有了个主意  跟你谈谈
And I had an idea that I wanted to talk to you about...
因为你在大公司上班
...because you work for a big company. Okay.
内线交易
Insider trading.
你有什么内幕消息可以给我
What information is there that you can give me?
实际上  他们不会告诉我们这些
Well, actually, they don't really talk to us about that stuff.
但我能给你些免费的涂改液
I can get you some free White-Out, though.
你照我说的做了吗  告诉她了吗
Huh! Did you do what I said? Did you tell her?
说了  她怎么说
I did. And what did she say?
"谢谢"
"Thank you."
不客气   她说什么
You're totally welcome. What'd she say?
她说  "谢谢"
She said, "Thank you."
我说  "我爱你"
I said, "I love you."
她说  "谢谢"
And she said, "Thank you."
不对啊  等一下  你说了你爱她
Oh, wait. Did you say you love her?
你想让她怎么做
Yeah, what were you trying to get her to do?
我现在怎么办
What do I do now?
欲擒故纵  疏远她
You play hard-to-get.
她已经在伦敦了
She already lives in London.
那你就去东京
So you go to Tokyo.
好吧  算了  别想了
All right, look, forget it.
别想了  你说你爱她   就已经完了
Okay, forget it. You told her you love her. It's over.
没完  你才完了呢
It is not over. You're over.
什么
What?
你懂的
You know.
好
Okay.
说得好
Good one.
还没完  因为她会给你打电话  告诉你她爱你
It's not over because she's gonna call you and tell you she loves you.
而她先前不说原因是  她感觉太强烈了  她害怕
The reason why she couldn't is because her feelings were so strong that it scared her.
你现在就回家  等她电话
Now, you go home and you wait for her call.
她很可能会从飞机上打  快去  走啊
She could be calling you from the plane. Come on, go.
要是她没打来  那就真的完了
Okay, okay. But if she doesn't call, it is definitely over.
不  等等  除非  最后我打给她  问问她怎么样了
No, wait, wait. Unless, eventually, I call her, you know, to see what's going on...
然后她说会再打给我  结果没打
...and she says she'll call me back, but then she doesn't.
那就真的  结束了
Then it's over.
够坚强
Way to be strong, man.
嗨  嘿
Hi. Hey.
我们能在这看卡通片吗
Listen, can we watch cartoons on your television?
我们需要休息一下
We need a porn break.
我们已经看了2小时的进进出出了
We spent the last two hours watching In and Out and In Again.
那  为什么不关掉了
Well, so why don't you just turn it off?
那我们不就成了关掉免费A片的白痴了
Because then we'd be the guys who turned off free porn.
太好了  你们都在
Oh, good, you're here.
嗨
Hey.
你手上拿的什么
What you got there?
这个  问得好
Oh, this? Well, I'm glad you asked.
难道你不讨厌用普通切肉刀
Now, don't you hate it when you have to cut a tin can...
去切易拉罐吗
...with an ordinary steak knife?
我知道你们在想什么
Now, I know what you're thinking.
"孕妇发狂砍杀四人"
Pregnant woman slays four?
你没买下这些刀子吧
They didn't make you pay for those knives, did they?
没有  确定
No. Are you sure?
没有
No.
你不能光靠卖刀来赚够钱的
You're not gonna make enough money to help Frank and Alice by selling knives.
不  我知道
No, no. I know that.
我只需要后续计划的本钱
But I just need to make enough money for the second part of my plan.
后续计划是什么  经销废弃物处理设备
What's the second part of your plan? My Saturn dealership.
哈罗
Hello?
罗斯
Ross?
艾蜜莉
Emily. Hi.
旅途还顺利吗
Uh, how was your flight?
糟透了
It was dreadful.
你对我美好的告白  我却那么回应  我觉得难受极了
Uh, I felt terrible about how I acted when you said those wonderful things.
不  不  没关系
No, no, that's all right. Um...
我很高兴你能打来
I'm just glad you called.
罗斯  我得告诉你这件事
Ross, um, there's something that I've got to tell you.
我另外有一个人了
There's someone else.
这句话在英国的意思  跟在美国一样吗
Does that mean the same thing in England as it does in America?
她不知道她想要谁
She doesn't know which one of us she wants.
我还是那个叫 "柯林" 的家伙.
Me or this "Colin" guy.
不应该是这样的  不应该有别人
This isn't how it was supposed to go. I mean, there can't be another guy.
真是的
Well...
当然得有别人
Of course there's another guy.
这样更完美
Heh. This is even more perfect.
现在你得证明你的爱
Now you have to prove your love.
我什么也不证明  我不听你的了
I'm not proving anything, okay? I'm done listening to you.
如果我没先听你的跑到机场去
If I hadn't let you talk me into going to the airport in the first place...
我就不会用拳头猛砸在墙上
...I wouldn't have put my fist through the wall.
你用拳头猛砸在墙上
You put your fist through the wall?
不  我没打着  砸在门上了
No, I missed and hit the door.
但砸的那扇门晃的可厉害了
But it opened really hard.
你得去伦敦   什么
You have to go to London. What?
你得去争取她
Yep. You have to go fight for her.
对啊  当然  太有道理了
Oh, yeah, sure. That makes sense.
你说你爱她而她却没回应
Because you already told her you loved her, and she didn't say it back.
然后打来电话告诉你另有其人了
Then she called you and told you there was another guy.
对  去伦敦吧   吓死她
So yeah. Go to London. That will scare her.
当瑞秋跟保罗在一起时   你做了什么
When Rachel was with Paolo, what did you do?
我嘲笑他的口音
I made fun of his accent.
你退缩了  你让他轻松得手  你完全没有去争取   没错吧
You sat back and let him have her. You didn't fight at all. Am I right?
你想让艾蜜莉也被抢走
You want the same thing to happen with Emily?
不想   那就好
No. All right, then.
去伦敦吧  去为她而战
Go fight for her. Go to London.
我是说  你和艾蜜莉也可以那样
I mean, that could be you and Emily.
这样  比他们还美
That, but nicer.
去伦敦吧
Just go to London.
真的  快去
Really? Come on.
到她家门口  给她个惊喜  别把她拱手让人了
Surprise her. Show up at her doorstep. Don't let her go without a fight.
好  就这么决定  我去
All right. All right. I'm going to do it. All right.
我要去伦敦  为她而战
I'm gonna go to London, and I am gonna fight for her.
好  加油
Okay. Good luck.
罗斯  你要到了机场
Ross, Ross. If you're going to the airport...
能不能帮我买那种特大号三角巧克力
...can you pick me up another one of those Toblerone bars?
我想到了  我想到赚钱的路子了
Oh, oh, I did it. I did it. I figured out a way to make money.
我要开自己的按摩院   让法兰克来帮忙
I'm gonna open up my own massage place and Frank's gonna help me.
配合他的时间来工作  那他就不必休学了
And we can work it around his schedule, so he doesn't have to quit school.
啦  啦  啦
La-la-la.
听起来很好  但你哪来的本钱
That sounds great. But how can you afford it?
我们在街上
We were walking down the street...
看见你们以前承包宴席办外烩的小巴车
...and we saw that van you used for catering.
我们就想到  让我说  让我说
And we realized... I'm telling it. I'm telling it.
你知道人们需要交通工具
Okay, you know how people need transportation...
但也需要按摩来放松
...but they also need massages to relax?
我们可以结合两者  我按摩  法兰克开车
So I just figured we could combine the two. Okay, I give the massages and Frank drives.
我可以改装一下车子  在后面安个床  你们知道我的想法了
I can fix up the van, bolt the table in the back and you know what I've got?
有进无出的死亡小巴
A place that no one will ever get out of alive?
不是  你们想嘛  就是给想放松的人搭的出租车
No, think about it. It's a taxi that people take when they need to relax.
叫轻松任你行
It's a Relaxi-Taxi.
名字是最精彩的
The name was my favorite part.
是我想出来的  你乱讲
Well, I came up with it. You did not!
不是  你想的是轻松之行  一点也不好听
No. You came up with Relaxi-Cab. That's not good.
哈罗  嗨
Hello? Hey.
天哪  你在英国吗  艾蜜莉惊喜吗
Oh, my God. Ross, are you in England? Was Emily surprised?
不  因为她还没回家
No, because she hasn't come home yet.
她整晚都没回家
And she hasn't been home all night.
很显然是跟那个人在一起
She's obviously staying with that other guy.
而我则是一晚上站在她家门口的大白痴
And I'm the stupid moron who spent the whole night outside her apartment.
好吧  下班飞机是几点
All right, when is the next flight out?
大概4个小时后
About four hours.
再等等几个小时  如果她还不出现  你就回来吧
Okay, just stay there a couple more hours. If she doesn't show up, come home.
告诉他 "轻松任你行" 的事
Hey, tell him about Relaxi-Taxi.
问问他  是不是听着比 "轻松之行" 好
And ask him if he thinks that is better than Relaxi-Cab.
不是轻松之行   是轻松车行   就像出租车行
It's not Relaxi-Cab. It's Relaxi-Cab. Like Taxi-Cab.
这个比较好
Ooh, that is better.
我们在伦敦吗
Are we in London?
你在这干吗  你不能在这
Why are you doing here? You can't be here.
我有话要对罗斯说
I've come to talk to Ross.
怎么了
What?
没事  没事
Nothing. No, nothing.
我本来想打给他
I was gonna call him...
你来说你爱他   我就知道
Oh, you came to tell him you love him. I knew it!
我是对的  我是对的吧  对吗
I was right! I'm right, right?
我更想跟他谈谈
I'd really rather talk to him.
我去过他公寓   他不在
I've been to his apartment and he's not there.
我得跟他谈谈
And I need to talk to him.
你们知道他在哪吗
So do you have any idea where he is?
罗斯  你在吗
Ross, are you there?
我不知道你听不听得见   我还是得说
Ross, I don't know if you can hear this, but I'm gonna talk anyway.
我在美国  跟你的妹妹和朋友在一起
I'm in the States with your sister and your friends.
后来我跟柯林分手了
And it's all over with Colin.
我来这就是要告诉你这件事  还有
I came here to tell you that and to tell you...
乔伊  你想要巧克力都拿走吧  拿吧
Yes, Joey, you can have all the chocolate you want. Just take it.
我来这就是告诉你  我爱你
I came here to tell you that I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
我现在就去电话亭   打电话给你
I'm gonna call you right now from the phone booth.
你听不见我
You can't hear me.
真想知道你听不听得见
I wish I could know if you'd heard any of that.
我想我  要么是刚告诉你我爱你  要么就是让邻居看了笑话
I suppose I've either told you that I love you or given my neighbors a good laugh.
纽曼太太  如果你在听   一边去  这没你的事
Mrs. Newman, if you're listening, bugger off. This is none of your business.
我想你八成是听不见
Suppose there's not much chance you did hear that.
有电话进来了
And there's the call waiting
我得挂了
so I should go.
就这样
Oh, well.
哈罗
Hello?
嗨
Hi.
罗斯  我爱你
Ross, I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨  嗨
Hey. Hey.
我刚才去银行  有个很火辣的出纳
I was just at the bank and there was this really hot teller.
但她没要我和她到金库去嘿咻
And she didn't ask me to go do it with her in the vault.
这事我也遇上了
Same kind of thing happened to me.
彼萨外送小妹来了
Woman pizza delivery guy comes over...
放下披萨  收了钱  就走了
...gives me the pizza, takes the money and leaves.
没说  "你家好漂亮  卧室一定很大吧"
What, no "Nice apartment, bet the bedrooms are huge"?
不  完全没有
No, nothing.
你知道吗  我们得把成人A片关了
You know what? We have to turn off the porn.
你说得对
I think you're right.
准备好了吗
All right, ready?
一   二
One. Two.
三   三
Three. Three.
感觉轻松了
That's kind of nice.
是啊  有种解脱感  对
Yeah, that's kind of a relief. Yeah.
想不想看看  它还在不在  想啊
You want to see if we still have it? Yeah.
免费A片   我们有免费A片
Free porn! We have free porn!